#### Contact

North Gate, FUTA, Akure 08129334848 (Home) opra.temmy@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/praiseoyedele-207226198 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Web Development
Computer Graphics Design
WordPress

# Praise Oyedele

Web Developer & Wordpress Expert Akure

#### Summary

Meet Praise a young, creative, and multi-skilled fellow. He specifies in the creation of beautiful and fascinating logos (3D, 2D & minimalist). Been tech-savvy, he engages in designing a responsive website, Onsite SEO, recommendation of hosting services, etc. With his pool of experiences, he can help detect slacks, proffer solutions and help businesses and organizations gain their ground and trust with their customers again. He has intriguing marketing strategies that allow converting perspective into paying customers. As such, you can trust him to help you with your marketing gigs and other things like your logo design and your website design in full from scratch.

## Experience

Climax Group Web Developer September 2021 - Present (5 months) Akure, Ondo, Nigeria

Fiverr
Web Developer
March 2020 - Present (1 year 11 months)
Nigeria

Pison Books Web Designer November 2017 - August 2021 (3 years 10 months) Ado Ekiti, Ekiti, Nigeria

## Education

Federal University of Technology Akure

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (December 2019 - November 2023)

baptist high school, ila Orangun SSCE, Science · (September 2009 - July 2015)

Federal University of Technology Akure Undergraduate, Computer Science